

# **CAREER OBJECTIVE**

Full stack Web Developer based in Munich currently graduating a 1-year intensive training program in Fullstack Web Development (MERN stack). Seeking a position to apply practical experience from several WebDev projects.

With an additional backround in both Law and Management, I offer result-oriented approaches, effective communication skills, analytical reasoning, and valuable teamwork experience.

# **SKILLS**

- HTML5/CSS3/Sass
- JavaScript Es6 / TypeScript
- React.js / React Native
- Bootstrap / Tailwind
- Node.js
- Express.js
- MongoDB
- Git/GitHub

# LANGUAGUES

- Portuguese: Mother Tongue
- English: Advanced (C1)
- German: Beginner (A1)

# CONTACT



+49 15235897629



marinna.dos.anjos@gmail.com



Ortlindestr. 11, 81927, Munich



https://marinnapereira.github .io/portfolio/

# Marinna Oliveira dos Anjos Pereira





# Full Stack Web Developer

### **EDUCATION**

#### **Fullstack Web Development**

05/2023 - present

DCI Digital Career Institute GmbH, Berlin

- · Accomplishing a one-year-full-time training including technogies from MERN stack
- Completing multiple small projects along with one final large practical project to improve programming skills

#### Web Developer Education Program

04/2023 - 07/2023

IGTI - XP Education College, Belo Horizonte

Introduction to Git and GitHub

10/2022

Digital Innovation One Inc., São Paulo

Algorithm and Programming Logic

07/2022

Udemy, San Francisco

IT Systems Projects and Introduction to Data Analytics

07/2022

Bradesco Foundation, São Paulo

**Computational Thinking and Programming Logic Essentials** 

05/2022

Digital Innovation One Inc., São Paulo

#### Postgraduate Program in Labor Law

04/2015 - 12/2017

Damasio Educational, São Paulo

#### Bachelor's Dregree in Laws

08/2009 - 06/2014

UFPE Federal University of Pernambuco, Recife

### RELEVANT PROJECTS

## Tea Point

- Creating a tea e-commerce website with register, login, cart and payment features
- Technologies: Vite, React, JavaScript, HTML, Sass, Tailwind, Vercel

#### To-Do App

- Developing a task management app allowing users to edit, check, and delete tasks
- Technologies: Vite, React, TypeScript, HTML, Tailwind, Express.js, Render

#### **Bulls and Cows Game**

- Creating a console-based implementation of the Bulls and Cows guessing game
- Technologies: Typescript, npm, Node.js

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Tutor | DCI Digital Career Institute

08/2023 - present

• Supporting students by facilitating their learning and mastery of WebDev concepts

#### Lawyer | Self employed

11/2014 - 11/2021

- Providing expert legal advice and representation in civil, labor, and consumer cases
- Successfully negotiating settlements which led to non-litigation resolutions
- · Conducting legal research to develope case strategies for favorable client outcomes

#### Administrative Assistant | UPE Pernambuco University 06/2018 - 03/2019

- Streamlining administrative processes by optimizing planning with detailed reports
- Comprehensively supporting stakeholders to foster collaboration
- Training new employees for seamless onboarding